<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mountains are calling...And we must go... - Articles</title>
    <description>A travel blog </description>
    <link>
    http://0.0.0.0:4000</link>
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Big Island, Hawaii</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;There are lots of resources on Hawaii online, honestly a bit too much and too many options to choose from. We had spent a lot of time in planning and it still underwent changes until the day of the trip which was bound to happen. In this blog, I have tried to give an almost comprehensive trip for 7 days so as to cover the whole island sufficiently well.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://0.0.0.0:4000/Hawaii-blog</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://0.0.0.0:4000/Hawaii-blog</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Garin Regional Park</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Garin regional park is one of the East Bay parks. It was the best place to see wild flowers blooming all along our path. For more information about the park visit their &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ebparks.org/parks/garin/default.htm&quot;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;. Extremely light on traffic early in the morning. People started coming late for a picnic with family. We saw hardly 10 people hiking in this huge park. They were all spread out. It was a peaceful hike with byfar the most number of sightings of animals/birds in a local hike in Bay area. We saw a lot of cows, by now we have concluded that we had underestimated the timid looking cows. We learnt our lesson to keep our distance from them. Apart from the cows, we also saw a bunch of turkeys on the way. As we came close to the end of our trail we also spotted 2-3 coyotes running from the top of the mountain to the bottom. We were 10ft away from the coyotes. That was fun !&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://0.0.0.0:4000/Garin-regional-park</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://0.0.0.0:4000/Garin-regional-park</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Vargas Plateau</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Vargas plateau is one of the East Bay parks in the Fremont hills. It overlooks Niles Canyon, Fremont, Union city and San Francisco Bay beyond. We went hiking during the month of March 2019 when California in general had good showers during Spring.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://0.0.0.0:4000/Vargas-blog</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://0.0.0.0:4000/Vargas-blog</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Mission Peak</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Mission Peak is one of the most popular hikes in the Bay Area if you are looking for some challenge. It is pretty crowded. We went hiking during the month of January when there were showers and there were green grass pastures for the cows to feed on.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://0.0.0.0:4000/MissionPeak-blog</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://0.0.0.0:4000/MissionPeak-blog</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Cayman Islands</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Cayman Islands - One of the lesser known Caribbean Islands. So why did we choose this ? Read along to know ..&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://0.0.0.0:4000/Cayman-blog</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://0.0.0.0:4000/Cayman-blog</guid>
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>
