<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
   
      <title>jekyller.github.io/test/</title>
   
   <link></link>
   <description>A travel blog </description>
   <language>en-uk</language>
   <managingEditor> </managingEditor>
   <atom:link href="rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
   
	<item>
	  <title>Vargas Plateau</title>
	  <link>/blog//Vargas-blog</link>
	  <author></author>
	  <pubDate>2019-03-16T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
	  <guid>/blog//Vargas-blog</guid>
	  <description><![CDATA[
	     <p>Vargas palteau is one of the less known East Bay parks in the Fremont hills. It overlooks Niles Canyon, Fremont, Union city and San Francisco Bay beyond. We went hiking during the month of March 2019 when California in general had good showers during Spring.</p>

<ul>
  <li><strong>Best Time of the year to Visit</strong>: During Spring after the showers when the meadows have turned green</li>
  <li><strong>Best Time of the day to visit</strong>: The park opens promptly at 8am</li>
  <li><strong>How to get there</strong>: If you come on 680, we need to take the Vargas Road exit and drive uphill on Morris Canyon Road</li>
</ul>
<iframe src="https://www.google.com/maps/embed?pb=!1m18!1m12!1m3!1d12655.46078836287!2d-121.93872812877207!3d37.575643088895006!2m3!1f0!2f0!3f0!3m2!1i1024!2i768!4f13.1!3m3!1m2!1s0x808fc109baa0c0bd%3A0xd9386b9e4a587286!2sVargas+Plateau+Regional+Park!5e0!3m2!1sen!2sus!4v1556772177576!5m2!1sen!2sus" width="600" height="450" frameborder="0" style="border:0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe>
<ul>
  <li><strong>Parking</strong>: The entrance has around 20 car parking spaces.  <img src="assets/images/vargas/vargas_parking.jpg" alt="Parking" /></li>
  <li><strong>Trail details</strong>:
    <ul>
      <li>Trail name: Golden Eagle Trail and Deer Gulch trail</li>
      <li>Strenuous level: Easy</li>
      <li>Total round trip: 4miles</li>
      <li>Elevation: Not too steep</li>
    </ul>
  </li>
  <li><strong>Things to keep in mind</strong>:
    <ul>
      <li>Restrooms are only at the trailhead in the parking lot.</li>
      <li>It can have large puddles of muddy water in the trail which you may have to jump and go</li>
      <li>Beware of cattle which may get aggressive if you are alone. Better to go in a large group.</li>
    </ul>
  </li>
</ul>

<p>We reached the trailhead at 7am only to realize that the gates open at 8am. We stayed in the car wondering if we should take a different trail but decided to stay and wait. To my utter surprise, a car pulled over just next to our car and a lady came running to open the lock on the gates. Although she was right on time at 8am, she apologized and was on her way out again. The wait was worth it to witness people keeping time and value others’ time on a nice Saturday weekend morning. :)
<img src="assets/images/vargas/vargas_3.jpg" alt="Trailhead" /></p>

<p>We started with the Golden Eagle trail. We were planning to go to take a small detour to the view point. We had to jump and struggle to cross the swamp at a few places but it was not that bad. Until we reached the point where we had to take a fork to reach the viewpoint according to trail map. We found that we were greeted by not so welcoming residents of the plateau, the cattle. 
<img src="assets/images/vargas/vargas_4.jpg" alt="Cowblock" /></p>

<p>We get a nice view of the city. Lots of cows grazing around.
<img src="assets/images/vargas/vargas_5.jpg" alt="Cityview" /></p>

<p>It is a pity that we could not finish the predetermined trail since we were the only ones walking while there was a group of rather angry looking cows almost ready to charge at us. We had to come back, couldn’t have risked, we being tiny creatures in front of the huge creatures if we get trapped with nowhere to go.</p>

<p><img src="assets/images/vargas/vargas_6.jpg" alt="Summit" /></p>

<p>We saw as we ended our hike that there was a board at the entrance put up which we conveniently ignored. 
<img src="assets/images/vargas/vargas_notice.jpg" alt="Notice" /></p>

<p>If you start with Golden Eagle trail and continue on the Deer Gulch trail to the end to see the views of Bay Area, it completes exactly 2 miles. Total round trip would then be 4miles with not so much of elevation. I highly recommend going there with a big group of people on a nice Spring day to this beautiful green pastures in the East Bay.</p>


	  ]]></description>
	</item>

	<item>
	  <title>Mission Peak</title>
	  <link>/blog//MissionPeak-blog</link>
	  <author></author>
	  <pubDate>2019-01-26T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
	  <guid>/blog//MissionPeak-blog</guid>
	  <description><![CDATA[
	     <p>Mission Peak is one of the most popular hikes in the Bay Area if you are looking for some challenge. It is pretty crowded. We went hiking during the month of January when there were showers and there were green grass pastures for the cows to feed on.</p>

<ul>
  <li><strong>Best Time of the year to Visit</strong>: During Spring after hte showers when the meadows have turned green</li>
  <li><strong>Best Time of the day to visit</strong>: The park opens at 6:30am itself and there will be people coming up late into the day as well. But if you want to beat the sun, go early as possible. <img src="assets/images/mission_peak/1b.jpg" alt="Entrance" /></li>
  <li><strong>Parking</strong>: There are two entrances- Ohlone college and Stanford entrance. The one in Stanford entrance has around 20 car parking spaces.</li>
  <li><strong>Trail details</strong>:
    <ul>
      <li>Trail name: Hidden Valley trail one the way up, crossing Horse heaven on the way and Peak Meadow trail while coming down</li>
      <li>Strenuous level: Hard</li>
      <li>Total round trip: 6miles</li>
    </ul>
  </li>
  <li><strong>Things to keep in mind</strong>:
    <ul>
      <li>Restrooms are only at the trailhead in the parking lot.</li>
      <li>Carry enough water to keep yourself hydrated</li>
      <li>It gets windy at the top, so carry wind jacket</li>
    </ul>
  </li>
</ul>

<p>We started hiking at around 6:45am in the morning with the sun peeking out slowly. The sky had turned violet and it was a bit chilly. 
<img src="assets/images/mission_peak/1.jpg" alt="Sunrise" /></p>

<p>We started with the Hidden Valley trail and the elevation picks up pretty soon with multiple switchbacks. It is one of the tough hikes in the Bay Area for a reason.
<img src="assets/images/mission_peak/1c.jpg" alt="Trailhead" /></p>

<p>We get a nice view of the city beneath the Mission Peak. Lots of cows grazing around but they were not bothered by the large crowd that went up and down the hill. Once you reach the top, it really feels mission accomplished to take the picture with the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mission_Peak#Iconic_%22Mission_Peeker%22_summit_pole">“Mission Peeker”</a>. It is an iconic pole installed in 1990 with time capsules containing articles and photographs inside it, to be opened after 2090.</p>

<p>It was a special day for Indians that day. It was January 26th 2019, the Republic Day and a group of fellow Indians hoisted the Tricolor Indian flag at the Mission Peeker. Felt proud to see it hoisted in a foreign country.
<img src="assets/images/mission_peak/4.jpg" alt="Summit" /></p>

<p>After getting some rest and having an energy bar we felt re-energized to climb down the peak. This time we decided to beat the crowd by taking a different trail - Peak Meadows trail. It is on the other side of the Mission Peeker. We confirmed that there was indeed a path to take us to the Ohlone College entrance from the people who just came to the top. They were more exhausted from the climb than us. As we climbed down we realized that it was steeper on this trail than on the trail that we took while coming up. Lesser people on this trail. But if you are not in shape, I recommend not to take this trail while climbing up.</p>

<p>The views of the green meadows are just breathtaking. I dread coming here in Summer where the grass would have completely dried up with Sun heating up in the morning.
<img src="assets/images/mission_peak/5.jpg" alt="Meadows" /></p>

<p>If you do Hidden Valley trail while climbing up and Peak Meadow trail while coming down, then it takes a total of 6miles.</p>


	  ]]></description>
	</item>


</channel>
</rss>
